《性愛大師》前情提要
Previously on Masters of Sex...
研究繼續進行了
The study is back.
你報名了么  一定要說你會的
Are you signing up? Please say "Yes".
肯定會的
Heck yes.
這是你今晚的搭檔
This is your partner for the evening.
我從來沒有過不舉的情況  從來沒有
I-I've never not risen... to the occasion ever.
我沒辦法干那個女人
The reason I couldn't fuck that woman
是因為我以為對象還會是簡
is because I was expecting Jane.
不舉在實驗中的地位也同樣重要
Nonperformance is an equally valuable part of the study.
你打算研究真實的性愛嗎
You're gonna study actual sex?
最后會的
Eventually.
也包括基佬的性愛嗎
Queer sex, too?
我在妓院碰到了一個年輕的男人
I met a young man at the brothel,
他是個娼妓  同性戀
a prostitute, a homosexual.
付錢找他的男人  有銷售員還有律師
The men who pay to see him, they're salesmen or lawyers
還有重點大學的教務長
or a provost of a major university.
這到底是怎么回事  比爾
What the hell is this, Bill?
弗吉妮婭  德保羅醫生
Virginia. Dr. Depaul.
醫生  所以如果有任何需要我幫你...
Doctor, if there's anything I can ever do to help you...
那就給我杯咖啡吧
I could use a coffee.
是心跳聲嗎
Is that the heartbeat?
莉比
Libby...
只要你看著我  然后告訴我
Just look at me and tell me,
孩子是不是保不住了
is this baby gone?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
發生了這些事  不是你的過錯
What happened was not your fault.
不是我的錯嗎
Wasn't it?
那是誰的錯
So whose fault was it?
你很強大
You are a powerful man,
但你也不是無所不能
but you are not that powerful.
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯 雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯： 面條打包子  胖兔純  roaddog  衛老哥
■
翻譯： 暴龍蛋   阿夏  王大可  不二兔子
時間軸：平林新月   燕窩窩窩頭   旅行的木訥
后期：孤帆     總監&校對：米小勒
■
性 愛 大 師
第一季 第六集
陰蒂高潮完全是一種青春期現象
A clitoral orgasm is a purely adolescent phenomenon.
在青春期之后
The proper response of
成熟女性的反應趨于正常
mature women upon reaching puberty
是因為人體會自發地
is a natural transfer of pleasurable feelings
將性愛的快感從陰蒂轉移至陰道
from the clitoris to the vagina during sexual intercourse.
在做愛時無法達到高潮
An inability to achieve orgasm through intercourse
是女性發育受阻的表現
is an indication of an arrested development in a female,
她的性冷淡需要通過精神療法來治療
whose sexual frigidity requires psychiatric treatments.
我的父親對女性性欲的見解
My father revolutionized modern thinking
為現代學界帶來了一場革命
with his views on female sexuality.
但在晚年  他承認
But at the end of his life, he admitted
他對于女性精神的理解并不全面
his understanding of the female psyche was limited.
"如果你想要更深入地理解女性"
"If you want to know more about the nature of femininity,"
他說  "你得求助于詩人"
he said, "you will have to consult the poets."
我相信
Which I'm sure
這話讓今天所有在座的醫生都如坐針氈
makes all you doctors sitting here today very nervous.
下面歡迎大家提問
I will now take questions.
你讓這里的女士很不自在
You're making some of the girls here uncomfortable.
沒事的  凱瑟琳
It's okay, Kathleen.
他只是來等簡的  又一次
He's just waiting for Jane... again.
我聽說她今天請假了
I heard she's not coming in today.
她是請了病假  還是
Did she call in sick or, uh...
她確實提到過要去看醫生
She did say something about going to see a doctor.
弗吉妮婭帶她走了
Virginia took her.
那個醫生叫什么來著
Oh, what was the name --
可能是羅伊德醫生  或是弗里德醫生
Dr. Lloyd...maybe or... Dr. Freed?
是  弗洛伊德醫生  我是弗吉妮婭·約翰遜
Yes, Dr. Freud, Virginia Johnson,
來自華盛頓大學
Washington University.
能在現場聽到您的演講我深感榮幸
It's a great honor to hear you speak in person.
醫生  您的父親認為
Doctor, your father's theory
女性通過自慰得到的高潮
that the female orgasm achieved by masturbation
與性交取得的高潮相比
is "immature" compared to one
是"不成熟"的
achieved through sexual intercourse,
這種論點曾被科學證實過嗎
has that ever been scientifically proven?
我不太理解你的問題
I'm not sure I understand what you're asking.
有沒有任何科學證據
Has there ever been any scientific evidence
能證實這個理論  比如說任何生理數據
to substantiate this theory -- any physiological data
能夠區分這兩種高潮的
that differentiates between the two types of orgasms?
就我個人而言
Well, I, for one,
無法想象如何能取得這種數據...
can't imagine how procuring such data would be possible...
更不用說其不得體性了
let alone decent.
希望沒打擾到你
I hope I'm not barging in.
當然沒有
No.
你還好嗎  孩子怎么樣
How -- how are you? How's -- how's the baby?
我們都很好  就是比較忙
Fine, we're all fine -- busy bees.
看看你
And look at you.
你去新做了頭發吧
You've done something new with your hair.
對  我幾周之前剪過
Yes, I had it cut a few weeks ago.
比爾和我準備去邁阿密待幾天
Um, Bill and I are going out of town for a few days to Miami.
我給席爾瓦打過電話讓他們不要送奶了
And I called Silver's about the milk delivery,
但我不希望信件堆積如山
but I didn't want the mail to pile up.
信的事不用擔心
Don't give the mail another thought.
你就坐在泳池邊好好享受邁泰雞尾酒吧
You just sit by the pool and drink mai tais.
我好嫉妒你啊
I'm so jealous.
我得走了  謝謝你
I'd better go. Thank you.
鄰里就是要互相照應啊
What are neighbors for?
你一定得告訴我你的理發師的名字哦
And you must give me the name of the girl who does your hair.
你看起來美極了
You look darling.
你拿到婦產科協會晚宴的
Did you get the minutes from
-安排了嗎  -拿到了
- the Obstetrical Society dinner? - Yes.
還有最新一期的《生育與不孕》
And the new issue of Fertility and Sterility?
以防我忘記  你的身份證
Oh, and before I forget -- your I.D.
現在你要扮演我的角色了
Now you're impersonating me.
希望你在安娜·弗洛伊德面前不要給我丟人
I hope you didn't tarnish my good name with Anna Freud.
不會的
Not at all.
不過我確實有點疑問
Although, I did leave a bit curious.
根據弗洛伊德的理論
So, according to Freud,
有兩種不同的高潮  未成熟與成熟的
there are two types of orgasms, immature and mature?
讓清潔工來做次大掃除
Have janitorial give the place the once over.
這里有的地方自杜魯門當政時期就沒掃過了
There's dust in here from the Truman Administration.
他認為一種高潮勝過另一種高潮
So he's saying that one orgasm is better than the other?
據我理解  他認為
As I understand it, he's saying
在女性進入青春期后
when a woman reaches puberty,
性反應會從陰蒂
there's a transfer of sexual response
轉移至陰道
from the clitoris to the vagina.
外部的或者說陰蒂高潮
The external or clitoral orgasm
只有少女才會有
is the province of adolescent girls.
成熟的女性與她們的丈夫做時
Mature women experience sexual response
會產生陰道內的性反應
intravaginally with their husbands.
否則就意味著她們性冷淡
Otherwise they're frigid.
但誰會相信這種說法啊
But who would believe something like that?
我的患者都相信
My patients.
這就是為什么我們有
That's why we keep the exam rooms
備有面巾紙的檢查室
stocked with Kleenex.
來我這兒就診的女性中
A quarter of the women
四分之一的人
who walk through my door
都認為自己性冷淡
tell me they're frigid.
可能是因為
Well, maybe that's because
她們的丈夫不夠給力
their husbands can't get the job done.
他是不是根本沒考慮過男人在這事兒里的角色
Does he ever address the man's role in any of this?
坦白說  弗洛伊德所有的理論
Honestly, all of Freud's theories
都有局限性
have their limits.
自從我大學發了一篇關于
I stopped reading him
戀母情結的論文后  我都不怎么看他的書了
after my college paper on the oedipus complex.
那段時間  我幾乎不怎么看別的書
I nearly put my own eyes out.
希爾醫生希望我看看
Oh...Dr. Hill wanted me
他那篇有關結腸和子宮內膜異位的論文
to look at his paper on colonic endometriosis.
又不是叫你去海邊看書
It's not exactly beach reading.
比爾  你真沒必要帶那么多東西去佛羅里達
Bill, you're not taking all that stuff to Florida.
太荒唐了
That's ridiculous.
1953年后我就沒去度過假了
I haven't been on vacation since...1953.
莉比需要些時間來調整心情
Well, Libby needs some time away.
你也是  比爾
And you do, too, Bill.
好想你哦  怪蜀黍
Missed you, stranger.
別這樣
No.
不這樣  那你想要哪樣
No? What's your pleasure, then?
我想知道
I need to know
你有沒有跟別人提及過我的名字...
if you've ever mentioned my name to anyone --
道出...我們的...
Disclosed the -- the nature of our...
真實關系
relationship.
你在問我有沒有到處跟人說你是基佬吧
Are you asking do I kiss and tell?
因為如果我說了  以后我就看不到你了吧
'cause if I did, I wouldn't have any repeat business.
你...你從沒...跟一個性研究者提過嗎
You -- you never... spoke to a sex researcher?
什么
A -- a what?
性研究者
Sex researcher?
他們是專門研究做愛的嗎
Are there people who do that -- they research sex?
我也想要那份工作
I want that job.
你跟我說實話
I want you to tell me the truth.
那我問你  我是唯一一個
Am I the only boy
與你共享過春光的男人嗎
who's ever shown you a good time?
你知道嗎  我跟你做愛的時候
You didn't strike me as a first-timer
你儼然一副輕車熟路的摸樣
when we got together.
也許是其他跟你搞過的男人說的呢
So maybe one of them told somebody.
聽著  我可不會攪了這種好事
Look, I wouldn't want to ruin a good thing.
還有...我想見你并不是為了錢
And...I'm not just saying that as a businessman.
我喜歡你
I like you.
也想再見到你
I'm glad to see you again.
我給你買了幾雙運動短襪
I bought you some athletic socks.
你總不能在沙灘上穿著花襪子吧...
You can't wear argyles on the beach...
除非你想學溫莎伯爵
Unless you want to look like the Duke of Windsor.
我還是沒有勇氣穿泳衣
I still haven't dared to try on my bathing suit.
當然  酒店附近有個天體沙灘
Of course there is a nude beach near the hotel.
我們可以不穿衣服...
We could leave our suits at home...
感受陽光撫慰著我們裸露的身體
Feel the sun glinting off our naked bodies.
對了  你是去另外一個地方
Oh, you're somewhere else.
和弗洛伊德去奧地利一處監獄...
In an Austrian prison with Dr. Freud --
"我們喜歡幻覺"
"Illusions commend themselves to us."
"是因為它們讓我們忘記疼痛
"Because they save us pain
取而代之的是愉悅"
and allow us to enjoy pleasure instead."
還是不夠嚴謹
Not the most rigorous science.
我讓南希·勞森去幫我去拿郵件
I asked Nancy Lawson to fetch the mail.
你真應該瞧瞧她看我的那個表情...
You should have seen the way that she stared at me --
好像在施舍我似的
Like I'm a charity case.
她就是個討厭鬼
Nancy Lawson is a bore.
他們都裝得跟沒事兒人似的
They all pretend like nothing's happened.
但我之前懷孕的事兒  他們都是知道的
But I was pregnant. They all know it.
佛羅里達沒人知道的
No one knows it in Florida.
忘懷過去  著眼未來
Better to focus on the future.
我一直在想我小時候的圣誕節
I keep thinking about christmases when I was a girl.
我母親去世之前  我們...
Before my mother died, we --
我們都會在壁爐旁邊的
We always had a big douglas fir
圣誕樹上掛滿襪子...
and stockings by the fire...
...還會給馴鹿準備一碟胡蘿卜
...A plate of carrots for the reindeer.
如果你沒成家  你還會往樹上掛襪子嗎
Do you still hang stockings if you don't have a family?
我們掛槲寄生
We'll hang mistletoe.
莉比  咱們家
Libby, we have a family.
有咱倆...
Just the two of us --
就夠了
That's enough for me.
巴頓  是你嗎
Barton? Is that you?
抱歉回來得這么晚
Sorry I'm so late.
被迫要和新上任的律聯會會長喝酒
I was coerced into having drinks with the new Dean of Faculty.
現在我可以直接跟董事會說他有多傻了
Now I can tell the board firsthand what a dullard he is.
斯高利夫人  你在看黃書嗎
Mrs. Scully, are you reading a dirty book?
從薇薇安那借來的
A loan from Vivian.
我也想趕趕時髦
I wanted to read it before I saw it.
人們都為之瘋狂
Everyone's mad about it.
"她的指尖撩過嫩白的雙乳
"She rubbed her fingertips over her breasts,
"這使得...
"and this caused
"她雙腿之間的某處有一種莫名的悸動
"an odd tightening somewhere between her legs
盡管她很困惑  但卻倍感愉悅"
that puzzled her but was, somehow, very pleasant."
我可不想咱女兒看這種書
I'm not sure I want our daughter reading this.
她還小  肯定事事都好奇
She's young and curious.
別擔心  會好起來的
Don't worry. This phase will pass.
我幫你還回去
I'm gonna turn in.
晚安  親愛的
Good night, dear.
晚安
Night.
好夢
Sleep tight.
沒事兒  我等下一班
It's okay. I'll get the next.
等等  我正想找你呢
Wait, hold on. I was hoping to run into you.
我近來一直走樓梯
I've been taking the stairs.
為什么
Why?
因為你想找我
Because you were hoping to run into me.
等等  那有什么關系啊
Wait. What's wrong with that?
我...解決不了你的問題  奧斯丁
I can't... fix your problem, Austin.
我也不需要啊
I -- I don't need it fixed.
又不是...
It's not bro--
聽著  我又不是為那事兒找你
Look, that's not why I was looking for you.
我在想
I was concerned.
凱瑟琳說你去看醫生了  而且...
Kathleen said you went to see a doctor, which...
是別的科的醫生是吧
A different kind of doctor.
對你有好處的那科
The kind you might benefit from.
泌尿科么
Uh, a urologist?
是精神科
A psychoanalyst.
你之前有讀過
have you ever read "On the universal tendency
《論愛欲中的普遍降低傾向》嗎
towards debasement in the sphere of love"?
就像《希臘古甕頌》那樣的嗎
Is that like "Ode to a grecian urn"?
那不是詩  是西格蒙德·弗洛伊德寫的論文
It's not a poem. It's an essay by Sigmund Freud.
我想你肯定會受益匪淺的
I think you'd find it very illuminating.
咱說話...能不拐彎抹角嗎
Can't you... Give me the headlines?
你老二沒問題  奧斯丁  你腦子才有問題
The problem's not in your pants, Austin, it's in your head.
上去嗎
Going up?
他在里面嗎
Is he in?
他在佛羅里達  度假去了呢
Oh, he's in Florida, attempting to vacation.
有什么能為你效勞的嗎
Is there anything that I could help you with?
告訴他我今天會帶著帕帕尼克勞醫生
Tell him I had Dr. Papanikolaou
來和他討論宮頸測試的相關事宜
coming in today to discuss cervical testing.
也許他愿意跟我們共進午餐
I thought he might like to join us for lunch.
帕帕尼克拉斯醫生
Dr. Papanikolas....
帕帕尼克勞
Papanikolaou.
討論子宮頸抹片檢查
To discuss pap smear.
你知道子宮頸抹片檢查
You're familiar with the pap smear?
我在盡量學習相關領域的最新動態
I try to keep abreast of what's happening in the field.
你提交的關于強制執行子宮頸抹片檢查的
Your proposal for mandatory smear testing
提案之前放在馬斯特斯醫生的桌子上
was on Dr. Masters' desk.
如果這個檢查是檢測男性癌癥的
If the test detected male cancers,
那你早就能在公告欄上看到相關文章了
you'd be reading about it on a billboard.
這個檢查在紐約醫院早就標準化了
The test is standard at New York hospital --
甚至在黑人病房都是
even on the negro ward.
但這里卻沒有
But not here.
如果我堅持提議總有一天會有的
It will if I have anything to say about it.
我準備開展一個臨床拓展項目
I'm going to start a clinical outreach program.
任何鄉村醫生都有能力做這個檢測
Any country doctor can perform the test.
只是需要有人指導他們一下
They just need to be taught.
這樣就可以解救無數女性的生命
That alone could save millions of women's lives.
我也許真的能幫上忙
I actually may be able to help.
我知道我沒有醫學學位
I know I don't have an MD,
但我知道如何才能
but I do know which strings to pull around here
辦好這件事
to get things done.
好吧
All right.
我需要弗蘭克醫生和坎寧醫生
I need Dr. Frank and Dr. Canin
為我的提案做保證人
to sponsor my proposal.
我需要得到
I need the official sanction
美國婦產科大學的官方認可
of the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists.
我還需要錢
And I needed money --
頭六個月大約一萬兩千美元
$12,000 for the first 6 months.
你能辦好這些事么
Can you pull those strings?
我從來沒見過這么多棕櫚樹
I've never seen so many palm trees.
簡直像剛果一樣
It's like the Congo.
只不過更熱一點
Except hotter.
預定名是馬斯特斯  六晚
The name is Masters. Six nights.
歡迎來到熱帶風情酒店
Welcome to the Tropicale.
你們這次是來慶祝什么特殊日子嗎
What, um, special occasion are we celebrating?
是我們結婚紀念日  十周年的
It's our anniversary -- 10 years.
如果是那樣的話
Well, in that case,
我想普通套間就太怠慢二位了
I -- I think we can do better than a junior suite.
他剛從西北大學轉校過來
He just transferred here from Northwestern,
一個昆蟲學教授  研究蟲子的
a professor of entomology -- bugs,
六十出頭  有點禿頭
early 60s, a little on the bald side,
但是以前沒結過婚
but he's never been married before.
一個禿頂的蟲子教授  結過婚才奇怪呢
A bald bug doctor. I can't imagine he has.
哈瑞特
Oh, Harriet.
別浪費時間了
Don't waste your time.
最近哈瑞特晚上有點忙  是不是
Harriet's evenings are a little busy lately, aren't they?
好吧
Okay.
莉歐娜想要讓我
What Leona is dying for me to tell you
告訴你們的是  我...
is that I, um...
我在大學里的一個人類性行為研究中
I volunteered for a study at the university...
做志愿者
on human sexuality.
這是為了科學
It's for science.
那個研究是比爾·馬斯特斯在主持的
The research is being supervised by Bill Masters.
他接生了我半數的孩子
And he's delivered half of our children.
我身上所有地方他都看遍了
And there's nothing I've got that he hasn't seen.
所以你說的研究  是指
So when you say research, you mean...
她是指性行為
She means sex.
和羅伯特嗎
With Robert?
在你們之間發生了那么多鬧劇以后
After all the ugliness you two went through?
不是羅伯特
Not robert --
是M-51-147號
Number M-51-147.
實驗是完全匿名的
It's completely anonymous.
你連他的名字都不知道
You don't even know his name?
我知道他很高
I know that he's tall,
我知道他頭發濃密
I know that he has all his hair,
我還知道  他教我的關于我身體如何運作的知識
and I know he's taught me more about how my body works
比羅伯特23年教我的都多
than Robert did in 23 years.
天哪  真的有那么不一樣么
Oh, god. Is it that different?
你知道那就像什么嗎
You know what it's like?
我的鞋
My shoes.
在我的成長期  我母親認為
Growing up, my mother believed
淑女就應該有秀氣的腳
that ladies were meant to have small feet.
所以她跟我說  你是六碼半
So she would tell me "You're a 6 and half.
你是六碼半
You're a 6 and half."
直到我二十多歲  我都在買六碼半的鞋子
You know, up until my 20's, I bought shoes that were 6 and half.
有一天  一個萬德沃茨的店員看著我
One day, a clerk at Vandervoort's looked at me
對我說  不好意思  小姐
and he said, "Excuse me, miss, um,
我整天看別人的腳  你絕不是六碼半
"I look at feet all day, and you are not a 6 and half."
我穿著一雙八碼的樂福鞋走出了那家店
I walked out of there in a size-8 loafer,
那感覺就好像  走在奶油上一樣
and it felt like I was walking on...whipped cream.
我知道為什么蟲子博士沒什么吸引力了
I can see why the bug doctor holds little appeal.
要盡快
As soon as you can.
當然了  先生
Of course, sir.
我讓他去叫客房送餐部送上來些香檳
I asked him to have room service send up some champagne.
這是個大床房  能睡下一整家人了
It's a king-size. Could sleep a whole family.
是有人在唱歌嗎
Is that singing?
好像是"鼴鼠跳跳舞"
I think it's "Pop goes the weasel".
現在又開始在床上亂蹦了
Now they're jumping on the bed.
幫我轉接前臺好么
Could you put me through to the front desk?
比爾  沒必要投訴
Bill, you don't have to complain.
我覺得我們隔壁要變成兒童游樂場了
It seems there's a jungle gym in the room next door.
我太太
My wife would be --
沒關系  房間很好  謝謝
Never mind. The room is lovely. Thank you.
我知道你想保護我
I know you want to protect me.
我們不能以后一直
We can't spend the rest of our lives
躲著別人家的孩子
hiding from other people's children.
我不認為那些是孩子的聲音
I don't think those are children.
《女性居家雜志》
Ladies' Home Journal
確實把這里評選為最佳蜜月地點
did name this the number-one honeymoon spot.
那雜志有特別指明是404房間么
Well, did they specify room 404?
周年紀念日快樂
Happy anniversary.
“愛之所在  欲望無存
"Where they love, they have no desire.
欲望之所在  愛之不能”
Where they desire, they cannot love."
那是什么
What's that?
弗洛伊德婚姻理論  應該是吧
Freud on marriage... I think.
我覺得我不太在乎一個男性心理學家說的
I'm not so sure I care what a male psychologist has to say
關于女性性行為的言論
about female sexuality.
他在抽雪茄呢
He has a cigar.
所以他肯定對自己言及的事情很在行
He obviously knew what he was talking about.
真的么
Really?
你想和你的父親睡覺么
Do you want to sleep with your father?
你希望自己有陽具么
Do you wish you had a penis?
我倒是希望這里的個別男人沒有
I wish a few men around here didn't.
跟你說說我的理論吧
I'll tell you my theory.
弗洛伊德是個壞情人
Freud was a bad lover.
有天晚上他發現自己的女人在用手自摸泄欲
One night he caught his hausfrau with her hand in her drawers.
自此他就開始懲罰女人
And he's been punishing women ever since.
有人摸我的胸我就能高潮
I can climax when someone is touching my breast.
你還能那樣  是真的么
You can? Is that true?
雖然不是經常  但偶爾會發生
Well, not all the time, but it has happened.
天吶
Wow.
他稱之為不成熟的性高潮  對嗎
He would call that an immature orgasm, right?
你真的相信性高潮有不同嗎
Do you really believe that there's a difference between orgasms?
就算真的有  他們也不會說
Well, they wouldn't say it if it wasn't true.
直到有人問起  他們才說世界是水平的
They said the world was flat until somebody asked.
那世界的盡頭在哪里
Well, then, where does it end?
我覺得弗洛伊德理論有其自身的局限性
I think that Freud's theories have their limits.
我是說  他不過是個心理學家
I mean, he was a psychologist.
而我們  是有科學依據的
We, on the other hand -- we have science on our side.
我們嗎
We?
比爾
Bill.
比爾  比爾
Bill, Bill.
關上門  關上門
Shut the door. Shut the door.
是他們  那對度蜜月的夫婦
That's them. It's the honeymooners.
那屁股跟黃鼠狼屁股似得
That's "Pop goes the weasel."
這次你的胸整個露在外面
So we will leave your breasts out of this entirely.
明白
Understood.
當你使用"尤利西斯"時
And while you use Ulysses,
我會監測你的情況
I'll be monitoring your vital signs
以及視覺圖像變化
and notating visual changes,
血壓  呼吸和子宮收縮頻率
blood pressure, respiration, rate of contractions.
你之前做過的
You've done this before.
但是之前馬斯特斯總在這
But always while Dr. Masters is here.
你覺得他會允許我們這樣做嗎
Do you think he'll be okay with us doing this
尤其當他出城不在的時候
while he's out of town?
如果數據很可觀的話  他肯定不會反對
If the data's compelling, he won't give it a second thought.
好吧  開始
Okay, stud.
弗洛伊德醫生的名譽就靠你了
Dr. Freud's reputation is depending on you.
別給他太多壓力了
Don't put too much pressure on him.
我們都知道接下來的結果會如何
We all know how that turns out.
還有記住  不要出現陰蒂刺激
And remember, no clitoral stimulation.
如果我不小心碰到了呢
What if I accidentally touch it?
我底下又沒長眼睛
It's not like I've got eyes down there.
簡  盡全力去做
Well, do your best, Jane.
當你用"尤利西斯"做完后
And when you're done with Ulysses,
有足夠長的時間來休息
then we will take as long of a break as you need.
然后我們用手部刺激再做一次
And we'll start in again using manual stimulation.
之后...  一切就留待事實說話吧
Then...We will let the facts speak for themselves.
心電圖數據走向是個T字
Eeg readouts match to a "T."
心臟反應完全相同
Cardiac response is identical,
其他生理反應也完全相同
as are all other physiological responses.
實際上  這次有輕微的上升
Actually, there's a slight uptick in this one,
在興奮度上
in terms of intensity.
是用"尤利西斯"的時候還是...
Was that the Ulysses or...
用手的時候
You. Solo.
我的陰蒂勝過我的陰道嗎
My clitoris beat my vagina?
太瘋狂了
That's crazy.
我想黃鼠狼又撅屁股了
I believe the weasel is popping again.
他們一天三次了已經
That makes three times in one day.
誰還去數那個啊
But who's counting?
他們肯定會精疲力竭而死
You'd think they'd die of exhaustion.
他們一定70歲了
They must be 70 years old.
教堂的杜利先生每天早上
Well, Mr. Dooley from church
能打一場完整的高爾夫  他都快80了
plays a round of golf every morning, and he's almost 80.
真可怕  精力旺盛堪比獅子了
It's uncanny. They're like lions.
當一只美洲母獅子在發情期時
Uh, when an African lioness is in estrus,
它一周內每十五分鐘交配一次
she copulates every 15 minutes for a week.
在女學生聯誼會里也有這種女孩
There were girls like that in my sorority.
上床吧
Come to bed.
她正處于停滯期
She's in the plateau state.
我們正是陽光燦爛時  放松點
And we are in the sunshine state...To relax.
我們可以用錢打發他們
We could, um, give them a run for their money.
讓他們滾蛋
Try to drown them out.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
沒什么
Nothing.
你在給他們計時嗎
Are you timing them?
他們是老年人
They're senior citizens.
他們的內分泌系統不再產生性荷爾蒙了
Their endocrine systems don't produce sex hormones anymore.
站在醫學角度看  這...
It's like from a medical standpoint, it's...
有點怪
Peculiar.
跟躺在床上的女人談論這個不太討人喜歡
And not very flattering to the woman who is in this bed
而正好這個女人是你老婆
who happens to be your wife.
好像是雷普利發出來的
It's like something out of Ripley's.
打擾一下
Excuse me?
我朋友告訴我有這個實驗
Um, my friend told me about this study.
你在找實驗者嗎  我想參加
You're looking for participants? I was hoping to apply.
你要找的是威廉·馬斯特斯醫生
You're looking for Dr. William Masters.
他星期一才回來
He's out until Monday.
不好意思  我朋友說她見得是一個女人
I'm sorry. My friend said she met with a woman.
好像是約翰遜醫生
A Dr. Johnson I assumed...
約翰遜女士是馬斯特斯醫生的助手
Mrs. Johnson is Dr. Masters' secretary.
下樓梯左側就可以找到她
You'll find her down the corridor to the left.
嬌小  皮膚黑  而且雄心勃勃
Small, brunette, ambitious.
謝謝
Thank you.
她不是個醫生
She's not a doctor.
比爾  我知道怎么看心電圖了
Bill, I know how to read an ekg.
我告訴你  幾乎難以區分
And I'm telling you, they're indistinguishable.
只是一回長一些一回短一些
Except one was a little longer and a little stronger.
想知道是哪回嗎
Care to guess which?
不想
I would not.
陰蒂高潮跟陰道高潮一樣
A clitoral orgasm is just as good
甚至比陰道高潮效果更好
as a vaginal orgasm maybe even better.
多虧了你廣泛的研究
Based on your extensive study.
這只是個開始
Well, it's a start.
這是個大發現  比爾  我就知道
This is something, Bill. I know it.
我唯一不知道的就是為何兩次高潮會相同
The only thing I don't know is how two orgasms can be the same,
即使使用的身體部位完全不同
since they involve two completely different body parts.
把電話掛了  去我辦公室
Put down the phone and pick up in my office.
我就在你辦公室
I'm in your office.
真的嗎  坐在我椅子上嗎
Really? In my chair?
其實是站著
Standing. Actually.
面朝門  十點鐘方向
Well, face the door -- 10:00.
從右數第三還是第四本
Third or fourth from the right,
有一本解剖學的書
there's an anatomy textbook.
這是羅切斯特大學的書嗎
This is from... The university of Rochester?
比爾  這是十二年前的書了
Bill, it's 12 years overdue.
幫我查一下倫理委員會
Refer me to the Ethics Committee.
從后面翻
Now, there's a plate in the back.
有一張女性生殖器橫切面的圖
Uh, a cross section of the female's sex organs.
看到陰蒂脛順著恥骨弓
See how the clitoral crura extend
幾乎延伸到骨頭處了嗎
along the pubic arch almost to the bone?
至少可以想象
It's at least conceivable that
弗洛伊德所說的成熟的性高潮...
Freud's mature orgasm...
只是另一種陰蒂高潮
It's just another clitoral orgasm.
因為陰蒂在兩種情況下都受到刺激
Because the clitoris is stimulated in both cases.
所以  意思是說...
So, uh, does this mean that...
你繼續講
Keep going.
意思是  女人根本不需要男人來施壓
Well, it means that a woman doesn't need a man to provide pleasure at all.
實際上  可能沒你們更好
In fact, we may be better off without you.
我想說的不是這個
That was not exactly my point.
現在也不要過早否定弗洛伊德的觀點
And let's not burn Freud in effigy just yet, either.
這只是一個單獨的數據點而已
We're talking about a single data point.
單純一位女性的表現不能概括整個研究
One woman does not a study make.
但為什么不能概括呢
But why couldn't it be an entire study?
等我回來以后我們再開始
We'll start when I get back.
導游手冊沒什么用
Uh, the guide book is useless...
除非你想看塞米諾族印第安人的鱷魚格斗
unless you want to see a Seminole Indian wrestle an alligator.
看來這沒什么用啊
This isn't working.
我覺得你看起來很漂亮
I think you look nice.
不  比爾...
No, Bill...
我以為出來散心會讓情況好轉
I -- I thought that getting away would make things better.
莉比...
Libby...
顯而易見  我們化解悲傷的手段不同
We obviously have different ways of grieving.
你...你需要你的工作
And you -- you need your work.
而我需要...
And I need...
今晚一定有回去的航班
there must be a flight out tonight.
我們可以...等秋天再來
We can come back... in the fall.
好好待上一個禮拜
We'll make a week of it.
我要留下來
I'm staying.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我想留在這里
I want to be here.
如果你對隔壁那對人
And I don't need you here
或者辦公室的研究更感興趣的話
if you are more interested in what is happening
我可以一個人待在這
next door or back at the office.
可我不能把你單獨...
Well, I can't leave you...
留在這里
alone.
如果這是你想留下的理由
If that is the reason that you'd stay,
那我情愿你回去
then I would rather that you didn't.
不  我...
No, I...
比爾  我不想...不想跟你吵架
Bill, I'm not -- I'm not gonna argue with you.
但我也不是在求你
But I'm not asking either.
回去吧
Go.
我看了弗洛伊德的那篇文章  說實話
Look, I skimmed that Freud article and frankly,
我覺得很多都是在扯淡
a lot of it seemed like bullshit to me --
那些關于母親的東西
all the stuff about mothers.
我才沒有戀母情結  好嗎
I'm not in love with my mother, okay?
你對文章的關注點的確耐人尋味
It's interesting that that's what you took away from the article.
那我們就來談談這個
Let's explore that for a moment then.
你是否對你的母親有感覺呢
Would you say you love your mother?
我母親和我勃起障礙沒有任何關系
My mom has nothing to do with my penis.
如果我們假設...只是假設而已
What if we were to posit -- just posit --
這種性研究讓你感覺到被他人評頭論足
that this sex study caused you to feel judged.
所以你想  回到一個不受指責的位置
Well, you'd want to return to a place free of judgment,
有這想法嗎
wouldn't you?
但在這個位置
But this is a place
你和一種類似于母愛的感情產生了聯系
that you associate with a kind of maternal love
而這種感情與性愛相聯系  讓你感到不正當
which, when sexualized, feels wrong -- illicit.
所以你的身體自行停止機能
So your body has short-circuited
為你解決了這個道德難題
as a means of solving the problem for you.
我完全不知道你在說什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我覺得你知道
I think you do.
不...不  我...我真的不知道
No. No, I -- I don't. I -- I really don't.
我覺得你知道
I think you do.
豪威爾護士  請至新生兒科室報到
Nurse Howell, please report to neonatal.
弗吉妮婭
Virginia?
斯高利夫人  您怎么來了
Oh, Mrs. Scully, how nice to see you.
我...我來和女兒一起吃午飯
I, uh...was just meeting my daughter for lunch
剛好路過  進來打聲招呼
and thought I might pop in and say hello.
薇薇安真的很不錯
Vivian is doing a wonderful job.
大家都很喜歡她
Everyone here just loves her.
她說你對她尤其關照
Well, she says you've been especially kind to her.
大家總覺得  像她那么漂亮的女孩
You wouldn't think a girl that pretty
不會有什么自卑情緒  不過...
would have confidence problems, but...
或許這是我遺傳給她的吧
maybe that's the one thing she got from me.
很抱歉告訴您  馬斯特斯醫生出城了
Well, I'm sorry to tell you Dr. Masters is out of town.
什么
What? Hmm?
您不是想跟他打聲招呼嗎
Oh, you wanted to say hello?
我想向你打招呼
T-to you.
是嗎
Oh.
你介意我關...
Would you mind if I...
沒關系
No.
我數到十  你們最好乖乖洗完手
By the time I count to 10, your hands better be washed.
亨利  我是認真的  你好
Henry, I mean it. Hello?
弗吉妮婭  我是比爾
Virginia, it's Bill.
比爾  太好了
Oh, Bill, good --
你絕對想不到今天誰來看我了
You will never guess who came to see me today --
媽媽  亨利什么都讓我來干...
Mama, Henry's making me do all of it...
比爾  我現在正在...
Bill, you know, I'm actually just --
正在給孩子們準備晚飯
I'm getting dinner on the table for the kids.
過會我打給你好嗎
Do you mind if I -- if I call you right back?
我在家里
I'm at home.
你剛才說什么
What's that?
我在家  我回來了
I'm back. I came back.
一切都還好嗎
Oh, is everything all right?
是...是天氣變了嗎
Did the -- did the weather turn?
莉比自己留下了
Uh, Libby stayed.
我想我們明晚可以再進行一次實驗
I think we should plan a session for tomorrow night.
為你的假設取得數據支持
Get some data on your hypothesis --
證明女性完全不需要男人
that men are completely unnecessary.
不好意思  小姐
Uh, excuse me, miss,
您愿意賞光和我們一起嗎
would you care to join us?
我們等了好久才等到位子的
It took us forever to get a table.
那太好了
That would be lovely.
謝謝你們
Thank you.
他們讓我們正好坐在出風口底下
They sat us over there first under an air vent.
真想不到在邁阿密還會這么冷
I didn't know you could freeze in Miami.
我妻子最反對空調了
My wife detests air-conditioning.
他卻恨不得睡在冰箱里
And he'd like to sleep in an ice box.
我能問下  你們...你們結婚多久了嗎
May I ask you two, um, how -- how long you've been married?
180年  因為表現好  減了幾年刑
180 years. With time off for good behavior.
我們是在高中認識的
We met in high school.
他是摔跤隊的隊長
He was captain of the wrestling team,
而我在啦啦隊里
And I was a pom-pom girl.
我第一輪就把她拿下了
I pinned her in the first round.
真的是太浪漫了
Well, I think it's very romantic.
在一起那么多年  看到還會以為你們是新婚
All those years and you could still be mistaken for newlyweds.
我可以告訴你訣竅
I'll tell you the trick.
你盡心盡力  把孩子們帶大
You shower your children with love
一旦他們年滿18歲  就趕快踢走他們
until they're 18 years of age, then you kick them the hell out.
這樣我們才能煥發第二春
Gives your marriage a fresh coat of paint.
我們有三個兒子  你呢
We have three boys. And you?
我有...我有一個兒子一個女兒
Um...I have a -- I have a boy and a girl.
我敢說他們一定像自己的媽媽一樣美
Oh, well, I bet they're both as gorgeous as their mother.
蒂米...蒂米是我大兒子  12歲了
Um, well, Timmy -- Timmy is my rock and he's 12,
蘇珊10歲
and Susan is 10.
等他們一滿18  立刻趕走
Well, when they're 18 years old, out.
告訴你丈夫
And tell your husband.
我丈夫已經去世了
Um, my, um... My husband is dead.
飛機失事
A plane crash.
你還戴著和他的婚戒  可憐的姑娘
You're still wearing his ring. Oh, you poor lamb.
這是很久之前的事了
Oh, it was a -- it was a long time ago.
剛出事的時候  我一直在想
When it first happened, I kept thinking...
一覺醒來  就會發現這一切都是場噩夢
I would wake up and discover it was all a dream.
但后來  我意識到
Then I realized it was up to me
過什么樣的生活  全由我自己決定
To decide what kind of life I would have.
天助自助者
God helps those who help themselves.
今晚的實驗都排滿了
It'll be a full house tonight.
你有沒有告訴他們等待他們的是什么
And have you told them what'll be expected of them?
兩次實驗  一次使用尤利西斯一次不用
One go-round with Ulysses and one without.
有一位報名者  我要征求你的意見
There is one candidate that I need to run by you --
瑪格麗特·斯高利
Margaret Scully.
你想把教務長的老婆招募進我們的實驗
You want to enlist the provost's wife?
她昨天來找我
She came to see me yesterday.
她看起來十分渴望做些貢獻
She seemed very anxious to make some kind of a contribution.
她指的是經濟貢獻吧
I'm sure she meant financially.
比爾  她知道我們的研究課題
Bill, she knows about the study.
并且希望成為其中的一份子
And she wants to be a part of it.
那她清楚她丈夫對我們實驗的保留態度嗎
And is she aware of her husband's reservations about the study?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我知道她并不打算告訴她丈夫
I do know that she does not intend to tell him about it.
她說得很清楚
She was very clear about that.
當然  我說了需要和你商量
I, of course, said I needed to check with you.
我不認為這是個明智的決定
I don't think it's a wise decision.
我們還讓洛琳·巴赫參與了呢
We let Lorraine Bach in.
她丈夫還是董事呢
Her husband's on the board.
如果她想要為科學做些貢獻
If she wants to make a contribution to science,
我們又為什么要拒絕她
Why would we turn her away?
好了  您想要些什么
There you are. And what would you like?
再來三杯雞尾酒
Three more daiquiris.
午餐就喝這么多
Mmm. So much for lunch.
人生得意須盡歡嘛
Well, you know, you got to get your jollies while you can.
赫魯曉夫已把手放在原子彈發射按鈕上了
Khrushchev's got his finger on the button.
只要一按  我們就要被炸飛了
One push and we're just dust blowing over aruba.
別這么悲觀嘛
Don't be so gloomy.
我是受不了看新聞啦
I can't bear to watch the news.
艾森豪威爾:美國陸軍五星上將 并擔任第34任總統
我認為艾森豪威爾像黃鼠狼一樣狡猾
I think that Eisenhower's a weasel.
我還以為你們喜歡黃鼠狼那樣的呢
Here I thought that you liked weasels.
額  我記得  你們好像住在我隔壁
I -- I think that you have the room next to mine.
402號是嗎
402?
墻的隔音不太好
Thin walls.
我家湯米曾經很愛聽那首歌
My Tommy used to love that song.
我晚上經常唱這首歌讓他入睡
I used to sing him to sleep at night.
不  你兒子到底叫湯米
No, is it -- is it Tommy...
還是蒂米
Or -- or Timmy?
額  他的名字叫托馬斯
It, uh -- it's, uh -- it's Thomas.
但我叫他蒂米
But I call him Timmy.
說來話長
It's a long story.
我猜我結婚已經...
Uh, I guess I must've been, what?
讓我算下
Let's see. Um...
將近20年  我女兒也都這么大了
Al-almost 20 -- my daughter's age.
那現在你們行房的頻率如何
And how often do you engage in intercourse now?
瑪格麗特  抱歉有些問題確實很私密
I'm sorry the questions are so personal, Margaret.
如果這讓你覺得尷尬...
Um, if this is too awkward --
不  當然不  沒事
No, of course not. It's all right.
謝謝你  比爾
Thank you, Bill.
額  你們都知道  巴頓很忙
Whoo, well, Barton's a very busy man, you know.
自從薇薇安出生以后
Things tapered off...
我們就逐漸減少...
Considerably after Vivian was born.
平均下來  你怎么看
On average, what would you say?
我們需要一個確切的數字
We just need to quantify it with a number.
一年一次  或更少
Once a year...Or less.
你的性高潮反應如何
And what is your orgasmic response?
房事過程中你的身體反應
Your physical response during intercourse.
額  其實也并不是很疼
It's, you know...not...really painful exactly,
更像是  在摩擦
M-more like...Uh, rubbing.
那是種摩擦的感覺
Rubbing -- it's a rubbing sensation...
要我說那感覺就是...  拖延
That can feel I'd say...protracted.
那這種感覺  有沒有逐漸增強為
And this sensation, does it build to anything --
一種愉悅
A feeling of pleasure,
一種渴望  還有肌肉的緊張
A kind of ache, a tensing of the muscles?
是會某種緊張感  有的
There is a certain tension. Yes.
你有體驗過釋放這種感覺嗎
And do you experience release?
你指結束的時候么  當然  完全的釋放
Oh, when it's over? Absolutely -- tremendous relief.
瑪格麗特...
Margaret...
你有沒有體驗過高潮
Have you ever experienced an orgasm?
我也說不準
I don't know.
可能吧
Maybe.
你應該知道
You would know.
我應該知道么
I would?
是的
Yes.
那就應該沒體驗過了
Then, no. I guess not.
我學得很快的  我自學了意大利語
But I'm a fast learner. I taught myself Italian.
你們給點提示  我一定...
I'm sure with a little instruction...
不好意思  我們的實驗對象僅限于
Unfortunately, this study is limited to subjects...
有過性高潮體驗的
That have had an orgasm.
沒有例外嗎
Without exception?
這是我們實驗的基礎之一
That is one of our baselines.
為了保證數據的連貫性
We've had to make it a hard and fast rule
我們必須制定下一些硬性規定
In order for the data to be consistent.
我們正在研究的是性反應的完整周期
We're investigating the entire cycle of sexual response,
從初始興奮一直到性高潮
From initial excitement through to climax.
是的  那是當然  這說得通
No, of -- of course. That makes sense.
我完全理解
I -- I understand completely.
我很抱歉浪費了你們的時間
And I -- I'm -- I am so sorry to have wasted your time.
瑪格麗特
Margaret.
比爾
Bill.
莫里斯
Morris. Is the, uh --
是音樂開太大聲了么  我可以關小點
Is the music too loud? I can turn it off.
天啊  我以為我們的房間已經夠豪華了
Holy moly, I thought our room was plush.
你這兒都可以停輛凱迪拉克了
you could -- well, you could park a Cadillac in here.
我從酒吧拿來了這個
Oh, listen, I, um -- I pinched this from the bar.
芭布和我認為
Barb and I thought
或許你愿意加入我們  一起喝杯睡前酒
You just might like to join us for a -- a nightcap.
再喝我看房子就要轉了
Oh, the room would start spinning.
我有一個辦法
Well, there's a cure for that.
你只要向著相反方向轉就行了
You just spin in the opposite direction.
我敢說你是位一流的舞者
I bet you're a bang-up dancer.
看看你  你身形優美得像個芭蕾舞演員
Now, look at you. You're built like a ballet dancer.
轉一圈
Do it.
再轉一圈
Again.
過來
Come here.
我們...該去找芭布了吧
Maybe -- maybe we should go meet Barb.
實際上...
Well, actually, uh...
芭布其實已經睡了
Barb turned in already for the night.
我或許...說了個善意的小謊言
I...told a little white lie.
-我的鼻子變長了嗎  -莫里斯...
- Is my nose growing? - Morris... hmm?
我還有另一種讓你神魂顛倒的好法子
I know another way to make the room spin.
芭布就在隔壁房間呢
Barb is right next door.
芭布也喜歡偷聽  跟你一樣
Barb likes to listen just like you.
你說什么
What? What?
但她是你的妻子啊
But she's your wife.
這么說吧  妻子就像家一樣
Well, your wife is like your home --
每天朝夕相對  所以你熟悉她的每一處
You live there, you know every nook and cranny.
但偶爾出去旅游一下總是不錯的
But it's always nice to travel --
不時換張床睡睡  你說呢
Hmm? Sleep in different beds.
請你離開  不然我會打電話給我丈夫
You should leave before I call my husband.
等等  你不是說你丈夫去世了嗎
Wait a minute, I thought your husband was dead.
你誤解了我的意思
Well, you misunderstood me.
好吧
Okay.
這道菜叫什么
What do you call this?
牧羊人餡餅[覆蓋土豆泥的肉餅]
Shepherd's pie.
真是人間美味
Just sensational.
伊桑那天晚上給我做飯了
Ethan cooked dinner for me the other night.
是嗎  做得怎樣
Oh? How was it?
他做的肉嘗起來就跟牛皮一樣硬
He made a piece of meat that tasted like a desk blotter.
希望你沒太打擊他
Well, I hope you were polite.
男人下廚的嘗試
It's always nice to be encouraging
總是值得鼓勵的
of men's efforts in the kitchen.
你父親連開水都不會燒
Your father can't boil water.
上次你摘扁桃體時我就給你做了煎蛋餅
I made an omelette once when you had your tonsillectomy.
你把墻紙都弄壞了
You ruined the wallpaper.
見過那些快餐店廚子怎么拋鍋翻雞蛋嗎
You ever seen the way short-order cooks flip eggs?
我們不得不換了整間廚房的墻紙
We had to repaper the whole kitchen.
訣竅都在手腕上
It's all in the wrist.
我挺喜歡那舊墻紙的
I loved that old wallpaper.
你們倆晚飯后為何不出去走走呢
Why don't you two go out after dinner?
為什么
What for?
我也不知道  換換生活節奏吧
I don't know. A change of pace.
可是都已經七點半了
Well, it's already 7:30.
那又怎樣
So?
去西弗餐廳吃個新地  或者去看場電影
Get a sundae down at Schiff's or...go to the pictures.
里亞托影院正在上映《冷暖人間》
"Peyton Place" is playing at the Rialto.
你不是還沒看完小說嗎
So what if you haven't finished the book?
你們還能趕上八點那場
You could make the 8:00.
不如這樣  你去吧親愛的
Tell you what, you go, sweetheart.
我知道你最喜歡那些煽情的玩意了
I know how much you like those weepers.
我的話估計撐不到下半場就得打瞌睡
I'd be asleep before the second reel.
你有時間嗎  馬斯特斯醫生
You have a minute, Dr. Masters?
我想弗吉妮婭已經下班了吧
I'm assuming Virginia is gone for the evening.
沒有  她去買三明治去了
Actually, no. She went to get sandwiches.
她一會就回來
She'll be back.
很抱歉那天錯過了跟你們一起午餐
I'm sorry for missing lunch the other day.
你和帕帕尼克勞醫生已經
You and Dr. Papanikolaou have known each other
認識很久了吧
for a long time?
我在賓州大學對細胞病理學開始感興趣時
When I became interested in cytopathology at Penn,
我們曾經交流過經驗
he and I exchanged correspondence.
他是你的導師嗎
And he mentored you?
不  他只是回答了幾個我的問題
No. He answered a few questions.
我沒有任何導師
I've never had a mentor.
他們確實...有一定的幫助
Oh. Well, they, uh -- they help, of course,
但那也不是必須的
but they're not entirely necessary.
沒有導師  你也一樣取得了出色的成績
You've done excellent work without one.
如果有更多女性先驅的話就不一定了
Maybe if there'd been more women ahead of me.
婦產科一直被男人所主導
Don't you find it interesting, Dr. Masters,
你不覺得很有趣嗎  馬斯特斯醫生
that obstetrics is a field dominated by men?
醫學向來就是男人的天下
Medicine is a field dominated by men.
就因為我是個女人
And at least twice a day,
我一天至少兩次被誤認為是
I'm mistaken for a member of this secretary pool,
醫院的秘書之一
just because I'm a woman.
與此同時  你的秘書...
And yet, your secretary...
你是說約翰遜夫人嗎
Mrs. Johnson?
難道不是"約翰遜醫生"嗎
Don't you mean "Dr. Johnson"?
你不在的時候病人都是這么叫她的
That's how patients address her when you're not here.
就像她是這主掌大權的人一樣
She acts like she's in charge.
她的表現一直很專業
She acts like a professional.
可能這就是為什么
If a patient mistakes her for a doctor,
病人都誤認為她是醫生
that's likely the reason why.
那她就該像個專業人士一樣
Then she should handle their mistakes
及時指正這個錯誤
like a professional and correct them.
約翰遜夫人利用她的姿色與魅惑
Mrs. Johnson hasn't earned those credentials
輕易取代了我苦學多年取得的學識與技能
and I take offense to a woman who uses her beauty and allure
這讓我很不能忍受
as a substitute for the knowledge and skill
她不配受到這樣的稱謂
I sacrificed years to acquire.
既然如此
So, why aren't you
為何你不去對約翰遜夫人說呢
having this conversation with Mrs. Johnson?
因為作為同事我敬重你  馬斯特斯醫生
Because I respect you as a colleague, Dr. Masters.
事實上  我還沒認識你時就被你的智慧折服
In fact, I admired your intellect long before I knew you.
但如今
But at this moment,
我所敬仰的頭腦似乎正被你
it would seem the mind I had so esteemed
另一個部位的反應所蒙蔽
is out-matched by another part of your anatomy.
我不禁猜想  如今
I can't help but wonder
你正在用哪一個部位做決定
which part is making the judgments.
我們來好好談談
All right, let's talk about this.
我不想談  你走吧
I don't want to talk. I just want you to leave.
就這樣嗎
Just like that?
是的
That's right.
我們不是小孩子了  我們是成年人
We're not kids, we're adults.
那就拿出點成年人的樣子
And we're going to behave like adults.
我吻了你  你也吻了我
I kissed you, you kissed me.
這是愛情  不是肉欲
That's affection, not carnality.
這是愛情  不是欲望
That's affection, not lust.
你該明白其中的區別的
You ought to know the difference.
你該如何稱呼一個男人
And what do you call a man
當他滿腦子想的都是...
who thinks about nothing but --
他就是人
Human.
《冷暖人間》  全彩放映
斯高利夫人
Mrs. Scully?
朗廷醫生  真沒想到在這見到你
Oh, Dr. Langham, w-what a nice surprise.
斯高利醫生也來了嗎
Dr. Scully?
他沒來  他不喜歡看這些
Oh, no, um, he couldn't make it. It's not really his cup of tea.
你那迷人的妻子呢
And your pretty wife?
伊莉斯九點就睡了  每晚如此
Oh, Elise is in bed by 9:00...every single night --
我們有三個孩子  你明白的
Three kids, you know.
而我卻在凌晨兩點以前都睡不著
Me, on the other hand, I can't fall asleep before 2:00.
我能陪您去取車嗎
Can I walk you to your car?
那太感謝了
Oh, thank you.
你是怎么對付你的失眠癥的
So, what do you do for that -- your insomnia?
我會去看電影  無所謂放的是什么
Go to movies -- doesn't matter which ones.
在大學的泳池里游幾個來回
Um, swim laps at the university pool.
那個泳池今晚關閉了
The pool was closed tonight.
我上大學的時候也游泳
I used to swim in college --
個子高對我來說是個優勢
the one place being tall actually worked to my advantage.
我的車就在前面
I'm just up ahead.
有時  我要是睡不著
Sometimes, if I can't sleep,
我就會在社區里溜達
I just walk around the neighborhood.
你知道奇怪的是什么嗎
You know what's strange,
當你在外面往里看時
when you're outside looking in,
總覺得別人家的房子泛著光暈
there's always a glow to someone else's house.
但是當你在家時
But when it's you inside,
你卻無法想象有人從外面看進來
you can't imagine anyone looking through your window
看到那樣的景象
and seeing it that way.
抱歉  那不是...我不知道自己在說什么
I'm sorry, that's not -- I don't know what I'm saying.
在我聽來你說的很有道理
That made perfect sense to me.
是嗎
It did?
你是個深刻的思想家
You're a deep thinker.
不會吧  我可不是
Well, not really, not me.
我已經讓董事會失望了兩次
I failed my boards twice.
但我不該跟教務長的妻子說這個
I shouldn't go telling that to the provost's wife, though.
我可以保守秘密
I can keep a secret.
你也許只是太緊張了
Oh, you were probably just nervous.
我做眼睛檢查的時候也很緊張
I get nervous taking an eye exam.
我...
I, um...
我最近參加了一項研究
I participated in this study recently --
算不上考試  但它是某種...
it wasn't a test exactly -- but it was kind of, um...
一種績效評估吧
a performance evaluation.
我真的壓力很大
The pressure really got to me.
醫院的研究嗎
A study at the hospital?
不提了
Doesn't matter.
每次我女兒要考試的時候  我都跟她說
Whenever my daughter has a test, I tell her
閉上眼睛  深呼吸
to just close your eyes, take a deep breath,
記住  你比你以為的懂的更多
and remember you know more than you think you do.
你都會想起來的  只要你...放松
It all comes back to you when you can just...relax.
這就是我
This is me.
我還沒有問過你
Say, um, I didn't ask you.
你覺得電影怎么樣
What'd you think of the movie?
我真是個傻瓜
I'm such a sap.
我一直在哭  你能想象嗎
I cried through the whole thing, can't you tell?
我平常不像這樣...
I don't usually look like this...
像什么樣
Look like what?
像...
Like...
像這樣
Like this.
歐耶
Yes.
你們得到想要的東西了嗎
Did you get what you wanted?
是的  謝謝你
We did. Thank you.
其實我在護士學校
I'm in nursing school actually.
是嗎
Oh?
所以這一切對我都很有趣
So all of this is really interesting to me.
真有趣  我之前以為你是個醫生
It's funny. I thought you were a doctor before.
我嗎  不是
Me? Oh, no.
你看起來很像
Oh, you act like one --
就像你念過醫科學校一樣
Like you could've gone to medical school.
然而我卻結婚去了
Instead I got married.
然后又離婚  兩次  還有了孩子
And divorced...Twice. Had kids.
等我知道我善于做這個  已經太遲了
I didn't know I was good at this before it was too late.
我36歲之前都不會結婚  我已經決定了
Well, I'm not getting married till I'm 36. I've decided.
而且我能照顧好自己
Besides, I can take care of myself.
用各種方式照顧好自己
In more ways than one, I guess.
希望你這樣的女性越來越多
Let's hope there are more and more like you.
因為當一個女人
'cause when a woman can
能夠像男人一樣取悅自己  或者更棒
please herself as well as man can, or better....
那將是一個全新的世界
it's a brave new world.
還需要多少才有足夠的樣本
How many more until there's an adequate sampling --
50個  還是75個
50? 75?
我不想讓你再做我的秘書了
I don't want you as my secretary anymore.
什么
What?
我很嚴肅的考慮了這個問題
I've given this serious thought.
你是要解雇我嗎
Are you firing me?
又一次  比爾
Again? Bill...
我覺得你應該換個頭銜了
I think you should have a different title.
能夠反映實際工作的頭銜
One that reflects the work you're doing.
因為你不僅僅是個秘書  對嗎
'cause you're not just a secretary, are you?
那我是什么
What am I?
你是研究助理
You're a research assistant.
而且你非常稱職
And you're a very good one.
我不會給你加薪或是單獨辦公室
I'm not giving you a raise or your own separate office,
但我們會找一個人來幫我們倆
but we'll get someone in who can assist us both --
一個秘書
a secretary.
有了秘書  我就可以把精力集中在研究上了
With a secretary, I could -- I could just focus on the work.
所以看起來正是時候
Well, it seems like the right time.
那你也同意我們正在進入狀態
So then you agree that we're on to something.
根據一系列未被證明的假設來做事
It's not science to operate from
不能稱之為科學
a series of unproven assumptions.
那叫武斷
That's dogma --
比如某一種高潮是不成熟的  另一種則是成熟的
like, one form of orgasm is immature, another is mature.
這也已經被我們用事實證明不科學了
Which we've just scientifically proved is not science.
但還有一些別的假設
But there are other assumptions.
比如
For example,
老年人的性活動會持續到什么時候
how long do elderly people remain sexually active?
一般的假設認為
Now, the general assumption is that
性生活會在60歲左右結束
the course of a sex life ends around 60.
但是我在邁阿密找到兩個70歲的例子
But I've got two 70-year-olds in Miami who are living proof
那是我們應該調查的事
that that's something we should investigate.
另一個問題  為什么有些女性
Here's another question -- why can some women orgasm
可以不經任何外陰刺激就達到性高潮
without any genital stimulation whatsoever?
可以嗎
Can they?
簡就可以
Jane can.
簡可以只被觸摸乳房就達到高潮
Jane can orgasm just having her breasts touched.
我可不太相信
That I find hard to believe.
不用勉強相信  咱們可以在這里試驗
You don't have to because we could test it here.
可以嗎
Couldn't we?
可以
We could.
還有一個流浪婦女
There was a woman on the road
只要把棉簽放進耳朵里就能高潮
who could orgasm by putting a q-tip in her ear.
今晚還有一個女人在問卷中寫道
And there was a woman tonight who wrote on her questionnaire
她可以在刷牙時達到高潮
that she can climax while brushing her teeth.
通過個人衛生得到性快感  挺好
Sexual pleasure via good hygiene? Okay.
男人可以在夢中達到高潮
Men can climax in their dreams.
女人也可以
Women can, too.
我想你的職務描述很清楚了
So I think your new job description is clear --
一直提問
keep asking questions.
好的研究者就該那么做
That's what a good researcher does.
但是  觸摸乳房就能高潮
Although, orgasming having your breasts touched...
我一定得看看證據
I'd need to see proof of that.
我們是科學家
We're scientists.
來看證據吧
Let's see.